(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering is ok
[Title: Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering is OK]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams
PENLIGHT COLORS
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams
Penlight Colors]
hololive Dreams
事前登録受付中！
[Title: hololive Dreams
Pre-registration in progress!]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams
Fan Message Board
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams
Fan Message Board]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Text: Attention - For Visitors]
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Text: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.]
声出し応援 OK です
[Text: Cheering loudly is OK.]
PENLIGHT COLORS
[Text: Penlight Colors]
ローソンへお越しの皆さん！
To everyone visiting Lawson!
2026年03月
[Text: March 2026]
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Text: Lawson Campaign Confirmed!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
This time, these six members will appear!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details scheduled for release on 3/9 (Mon)!
ホロライブ スーパー エキスポ 2026、バンダイブースを開催！
Hosting the Bandai booth at Hololive Super Expo 2026!
注目の新商品も初公開！
Featuring the first reveal of hot new items!
オリジナルフレームで撮影！
Take photos with original frames!
あなただけのカードデザイン！
Create your very own card design!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get a limited card at the booth!
連動プロジェクトも公開！
Collaboration projects will also be revealed!
待ってるよー！
We'll be waiting for you!
hololive 1st fes. Nonstop Story
[Title: hololive 1st fes. Nonstop Story]
hololive 2nd fes. Beyond the Stage
[Title: hololive 2nd fes. Beyond the Stage]
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
[Title: hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish]
hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade
[Title: hololive 4th fes. Our Bright Parade]
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
[Title: hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment]
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
[Title: hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定!!
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin'on Dreams - Now on JOYSOUND Miruhaco!!]
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Because you were there...
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
...I want to say "thank you" over and over again.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now!
さあ乗り込もう！ Ridin' on Dreams
Alright, let's get on board! Ridin' on Dreams!
Yeah！！
Yeah!!
Wow oh oh…
Hey！！ (Hey！！)
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah！！
Yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream...
想像できないような
...to something unimaginable...
想いになったんだ
...this feeling has truly grown.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement just won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost...
絆が舵になる
...our bond will be our rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even the slightest bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...we can just blow it all away!
Ridin' on Dreams - hololive 7th fes.
[Title: Ridin' on Dreams - hololive 7th fes.]
Yeah！！Wow oh oh…Hey！！ (Hey！！) Hey！！ (Hey！！)Yeah！！
Yeah!! Wow oh oh... Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から想像できないような想いになったんだ
Ah, a small dream turned into feelings I couldn't have imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら絆が舵になる
No matter how many times we get lost, our bond becomes our rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
Even a little bit of anxiety, we can just blow it away.
果てない旅路を今漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There will surely be hardships as we row through this endless journey.
それも力に変えて一緒に進むんだよ！
Let's turn that into strength and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう “らしく” 輝いていたい
Let's overcome the rough waves, I want to keep shining as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you...
ねえ、宝物だ から
...is a treasure to me.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って 地図など無い 未知の世界で
Holding hands, calling out to each other, in an unknown world with no map.
まだまだ行こう！Ridin' on Dreams
Let's keep going! Ridin' on Dreams.
Wow oh oh…Hey！！ (Hey！！) Hey！！ (Hey！！)Yeah！！
Wow oh oh... Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの行く先乱そうとも
Even if a sudden wind tries to disturb our path,
あの日誓ったんだ覚悟は揺ルがない
I made a vow that day, my resolve will not waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中明日への橋になる
Thinking "I have to do this right!" becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね “あたりまえ”は無いから
I have to cherish it more, because nothing is taken for granted.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
[Notice: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.]
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 未完成も愛して
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, love even the imperfections.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 想いは一つだ
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, our feelings are as one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 僅かな希望でも
Wow oh oh oh oh oh, even with just a sliver of hope,
僕と 君で ずっと 馬鹿にされても 信じたい！
You and me, forever, I want to believe even if they make fun of us!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ ずっと一緒だよ！
Hey, my feelings are overflowing, we'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう “らしく” 輝いていたい
Let's overcome the rough waves, I want to keep shining as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you,
ねえ、宝物だから
is a treasure to me.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って 地図など無い 未知の世界で
Holding hands, calling out to each other, in an unknown world with no map.
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない 何度でも立ち上がってさ
You're not alone, we'll stand up again and again.
笑い合っていたい 願ねがいだって みんなで、さあ！
I want to keep laughing together, even our wishes, all of us together, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！Ridin' on Dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on Dreams.
Wow oh oh…Hey！！ (Hey！！) Hey！！ (Hey！！)Yeah！！
Wow oh oh... Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over again.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう! Ridin’ on Dreams Yeah!!
Alright, let's get on board! Ridin' on Dreams Yeah!!
Wow oh oh… Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream,
想像できないような
it became a feeling
想いになったんだ
I never could have imagined.
わくわく止まらない!
The excitement just won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
can be blown away!
果てない旅路を今 漕いでる途中に
On this endless journey we're rowing right now,
困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships too.
それも力に変えて
But we'll turn those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ!
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく” 輝いていたい
I want to shine as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だ から
is such a treasure.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう! Ridin’ on Dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh… Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disturb our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
I made a vow that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
My resolution won't waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ!って背中
A bridge to tomorrow starts
明日への橋になる
with a back that thinks "I have to do this right!"
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to treasure it more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing can be taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat...
どっから始めたらいいか
Wondering where to start,
もがいて 少しずつね
struggling, little by little,
輪になって 見つけた
we formed a circle and found
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that can't be replaced.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 未完成も愛して
Wow oh oh... Love even the incompleteness.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 想いは一つだ
Wow oh oh... Our thoughts are one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh 僅かな希望でも
Wow oh oh... Even if it's a tiny hope,
僕と 君で ずっと
you and I, forever,
馬鹿にされても 信じたい!
even if we're mocked, I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are just overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ!
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく” 輝いていたい
I want to shine as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
is such a treasure.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Getting up again and again,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together.
願いだって みんなで、さあ!
Our wishes, everyone together, come on!
手をつないで 想像も超えて
Hold hands and go beyond our imagination.
まだまだ行こう! Ridin’ on Dreams
Let's keep going! Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh… Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves together.
“らしく” 輝いていたい
I want to shine as myself.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I met you
ねえ、宝物だから
is such a treasure.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You're not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Getting up again and again,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together.
願いだって みんなで、さあ!
Our wishes, everyone together, come on!
手をつないで 想像も超えて
Hold hands and go beyond our imagination.
まだまだ行こう! Ridin’ on Dreams
Let's keep going! Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh… Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!) Yeah!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
眠たいな 行きたくないな
I want to sleep, I don't want to go
でも行かなきゃ いかなきゃ
But I have to go, I have to go
あしたは月曜日
It's Monday tomorrow
もうすでにもうすでに
I'm already feeling tired, I'm already feeling like...
気が重いな 気が重いな
I want to go back to sleep, I want to go back to sleep
起き上がりたくないな
I don't want to wake up
ベッドから出たくないな
I don't want to leave my bed
でも目覚ましは鳴るし
But the alarm clock is ringing
世界は僕を呼ぶんだ
And the world is calling me
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
眠たいな 行きたくないな
I want to sleep, I don't want to go
でも行かなきゃ いかなきゃ
But I have to go, I have to go
あしたは月曜日
It's Monday tomorrow
もうすでにもうすでに
I'm already feeling tired, I'm already feeling like...
気が重いな 気が重いな
I want to go back to sleep, I want to go back to sleep
起き上がりたくないな
I don't want to wake up
ベッドから出たくないな
I don't want to leave my bed
でも目覚ましは鳴るし
But the alarm clock is ringing
世界は僕を呼ぶんだ
And the world is calling me
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あじまる
[Text: Ajimaru]
これが星街再演 サインぬい!!!!!!
[Text: This is the Hoshimachi Reenactment: Signed plushie!!!!!!]
ローチケ当たったので... 解散かも？
[Text: Won the Lawson ticket... so maybe we're disbanding?]
声出せ!!
[Text: Make some noise!!]
Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
眠たいな 行きたくないな
I want to sleep, I don't want to go
でも行かなきゃ いかなきゃ
But I have to go, I have to go
あしたは月曜日
It's Monday tomorrow
もうすでにもうすでに
I'm already feeling tired, I'm already feeling like...
気が重いな 気が重いな
I want to go back to sleep, I want to go back to sleep
起き上がりたくないな
I don't want to wake up
ベッドから出たくないな
I don't want to leave my bed
でも目覚ましは鳴るし
But the alarm clock is ringing
世界は僕を呼ぶんだ
And the world is calling me
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
で声出しして行こう
[Text: Let's go and make some noise]
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
眠たいな 行きたくないな
I want to sleep, I don't want to go
でも行かなきゃ いかなきゃ
But I have to go, I have to go
あしたは月曜日
It's Monday tomorrow
もうすでにもうすでに
I'm already feeling tired, I'm already feeling like...
気が重いな 気が重いな
I want to go back to sleep, I want to go back to sleep
起き上がりたくないな
I don't want to wake up
ベッドから出たくないな
I don't want to leave my bed
でも目覚ましは鳴るし
But the alarm clock is ringing
世界は僕を呼ぶんだ
And the world is calling me
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
がんばろう がんばろう
Let's do our best, let's do our best
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
眠たいな 行きたくないな
I want to sleep, I don't want to go
でも行かなきゃ...
But I have to go...
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, the words we've layered,
届け
reach out!
Yeah!
色とりどりに 描いては
Painting in various colors,
ぎこちないと 笑ってた
we laughed, saying it was awkward.
未来予想 あの日の続きを 見よう
Let's see the continuation of our future plan.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, even wearing the wind,
扉を叩いて 進んでくよ
knocking on doors, we move forward.
どんなことも きっと 一緒なら 叶えていける
Surely, together, we can make it all come true.
La la la...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, the words we've layered,
鮮やかな 日々の向こう
beyond the vibrant days,
いつも君と 歌ってるよ ストーリー
I'm always singing with you, our story.
ハートに 結んだ夢が
The dream tied to my heart
空へ 駆けてゆく
rides toward the sky.
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
Carrying the sparkle to you,
届け メロディ どこまでも
reach out, melody, forever.
Wow oh oh...
何気ないことを 思い出す
Recalling casual things,
一人じゃないよって 深呼吸
take a deep breath, saying 'I'm not alone'.
見たい景色 楽しもう 魔法の言葉
Let's enjoy the view with those magic words.
一息ついて 遠くを眺めて
Taking a breath, gazing into the distance,
また君を知って 旅の度に
getting to know you again with every journey,
ちょっと勇気出して 明日へと 飛んでいけ
With a bit of courage, fly toward tomorrow.
La la la...
降り積もる 道しるべは まだ
The signs that pile up are still...
La la la...
覚えてる
I remember,
歌...
the song...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, the words we've layered.
Prism Melody
[Song: Prism Melody]
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony, once I reach out my hand
足跡に虹がかかる
A rainbow appears over my footprints
君と晴れる 打ち抜くようなステージ
Clearing up with you on this striking stage
ハーモニー 印した場所へ
Harmony, towards the place we marked
運ぶ約束を 輝きに乗せて
Carrying our promise, riding on the radiance
世界へ響け メロディ
Resonate to the world, melody
いつまでも 君と
Forever, with you
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That one step I took with you, that moment
宝物だって胸を張る今
Now I can proudly say it's a treasure
歩いて 走って はしゃいで 笑って行くんだ
Walking, running, frolicking, laughing, we go on
色褪せないまま
While staying unfaded
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Our voices mixing together, look
聴こえてる
I can hear it
ハーモニー 重ねたことが
Harmony, the things we've layered
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond the vivid days
ずっと君と 彩る物語
A story colored forever with you
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Harmony, the connected dreams
空へ駆けてゆく
Galloping towards the sky
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
Riding on the sparkle, to you
世界へ響け 愛を
Resonate to the world, love
メロディ どこまでも
Melody, everywhere
パレット パレット パレット 輝くんだよ
Palette, Palette, Palette, it's shining
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal
パレット パレット パレット 探しに行く
Palette, Palette, Palette, going to search
スタートは何度だって
The start is as many times as it takes
独り言 続くただ
Monologue just continuing
始まりたかったんだ
I simply wanted to begin
暗がりに灯った
Lit up in the darkness
それは眩しすぎた名前
That was a name far too dazzling
それは優しすぎる夜で
That was a night far too kind
もっと 近づけて手を伸ばした
Getting closer, I reached out my hand
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly connected
ほら 今 僕ら物語になった
Look, now we've become a story
パレット パレット パレット 輝くんだよ
Palette, Palette, Palette, it's shining
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring your frustrations and your dearness with you
風に夢 跳ね 飛び立てるさ
Dreams bouncing in the wind, we can take flight
ささやかな祈り光り
Faint prayers shining
終わりなき兆し
Endless signs
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよう
So I can be proud of finding you
ここから これから カラフル パレット パレット パレット
From here, from now on, colorful Palette, Palette, Palette
君と在ることなんだ
It's to be with you
“ただいま”を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home"
“おかえり”って叫ぶよ
I'll shout "welcome back"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Let's shine
暗がりを満たすのは
Filling the darkness...
君だ 僕だ！
...is you and me!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Let's shine
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring your regrets and your love along
風、夢、羽
Wind, dreams, wings
飛び立てるさ
We can fly
ささやかな祈りは 光
A small prayer is a light
終わりなき 兆し
An endless sign
君と 飛び込んでゆく
Diving in with you
素敵なスタートさ
A wonderful start
ここから これから
From here, from now on
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
それじゃあ、次のステージ、スタートです！
Well then, let's start the next stage!
Watch out!!
Warning! Warning! 隣り合わせで
Warning! Warning! Side by side
May God bless you 言葉の綾ね
May God bless you, just a figure of speech
Warning! Warning! 彷徨いながら
Warning! Warning! While wandering
I will stay true to myself 'cause of you
hololive 7th fes. 「Bright Parade」!
hololive 7th fes. "Bright Parade"!
まだまだ盛り上がっていこうぜ！最後までよろしく！
Let's keep the energy up! Stick with me until the end!
「はじめから」みたいに
Just like "from the beginning"
何もない世界に 理不尽に囚われる
Caught unreasonably in a world of nothing
黙ってしまうほどの恐怖はない
There's no fear that makes me fall silent
使い捨てるみたいに 手を離したあなたに
To you who let go of my hand as if discarding me
「昨日とはまるで違う」って
Saying "it's completely different from yesterday"
わかったところで しょうもない
Even if I understand it, it's pointless
変わっていく身体と
With my changing body
心の中で響く voice
And the voice echoing in my heart
間違ってなかったと
That I wasn't wrong
ただ この空を眺めてる
I'm simply staring at this sky
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time we overlap
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I brush it off...
確かにあった後悔から？
...is it because of the regrets that were definitely there?
誓ったはずなんだ
I was supposed to have sworn
さよならすら シルべにしよう
To make even a goodbye a guidepost
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
As if wishing every time I touch the light
And still I rise!!
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to be stained
越えられない border
An uncrossable border
揺れる意志を convert
Convert my wavering will
嘘で染めるような日々じゃ
In days dyed with lies
振り返った時には heartache
When looking back, it's heartache
また夜が明ける wake up
The night breaks again, wake up
夢の中の flavor
The flavor within my dreams
誰もいなくなった道を歩いている
Walking down a path where no one is left
今の私に 迷いすら重ねてくる
Even hesitation piles up on me now
おとぎ話の正体
The true form of a fairy tale
誤魔化しきれなかった
I couldn't hide it completely
心が纏う熱を 憧れが照らしてる
The heat my heart wears is lit by longing
I still 重なってくたび
I still, every time we overlap
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I brush it off...
大人になった後悔から？
...is it because of the regrets of having grown up?
月明かりの夜は
On a moonlit night
さよならすら シルべにしよう
Let even a goodbye be a guidepost
光を繋ぐたび 浮かぶ星座のように
Like constellations floating as I connect the light
選んできた道のりを 今を
The path I've chosen, the present...
いずれ後悔してしまう時が来ても
...even if a time of regret comes eventually
私はまだ止まらない。
I still won't stop.
「ねえ、聞いてよ」
"Hey, listen."
また君は、僕の知らない誰かの話を。
You talk again about someone I don't know.
[どれも哀を模した。]
[Song Title: Each one imitates sorrow.]
[どれも愛を模した。]
[Each one imitates love.]
ハイ！皆様！
Hi, everyone!
この口元は愛しのマトイ！？
Is this mouth the beloved target!?
今すぐ抱きしめてチュチュチュってしたいよ！
I want to hug you and go 'chu-chu-chu' right now!
待っててね！ダーリン！もう破裂しちゃう！
Wait for me, Darling! I'm about to explode!
抑えきれないの
I can't hold it back,
私の跡がクチュクチュしてる
my marks are tingling.
潤んだ瞳 蕩まく唇
Moist eyes, melting lips,
無邪気な笑顔
an innocent smile.
もう止まらないの
It won't stop anymore,
私の中の何かがグズグズ
something inside of me is stirring,
溢れ出しちゃう
it's about to overflow.
あー！
Ahhh!
頭の芯までビンビン感じちゃう
I can feel it vibrating to the core of my head.
お空から降る ハニーお餅くん！？
Honey Omochi-kun falling from the sky!?
隠れてないで お顔見せて
Don't hide, show me your face.
風通し良好 100パーセント！
Good ventilation, 100 percent!
出力最大！
Maximum output!
ほっ！
Ho!
みーつけた！
Found you!
胸がキュンキュン
My heart is pounding,
愛は止まらないの
my love won't stop.
好き好き 大好き
I love you, I love you so much,
マリーミー！
Marry me!
私だけのお姫様も
Even my very own princess,
離さない ずっと
I'll never let go, forever.
境界で四季をあげましょう
Let's offer up the seasons at the boundary,
神様だって怖くない
even God is not scary.
思い立ったので行っちゃおー！
I've made up my mind, so let's go!
ハネムーン！
Honeymoon!
チュッ！ お嫁 ハネムーン！
Chu! Bride honeymoon!
寂しくないの？ ダーリン
Aren't you lonely, Darling?
お帰りのチュッは？
Where's my welcome-home kiss?
チュッ！
Chu!
さて ご飯にしようかな お風呂にしようかな
Now, should I make dinner? Or should I take a bath?
それとも...
Or maybe...
私？
Me?
今日はこれから二人で楽しいショッピングデート！
Today, from now on, it's a fun shopping date for the two of us!
ダーリンも準備できてる？
Are you ready too, Darling?
ダーリン どこにいるの？
Darling, where are you?
もしかして ネネとかくれんぼしてるのかな？
Are you maybe playing hide-and-seek with Nene?
テーブルの下？ クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Inside the closet?
よーし ネネ 本気出しちゃうぞ！
Alright, Nene's going all out!
100パーセント！
100 percent!
甘い鼓動のリズム
The rhythm of a sweet heartbeat,
赤い糸で二人繋がっているの
we're connected by a red thread of fate.
ハートがビンビン
My heart is throbbing,
カモンベイベー
Come on baby!
みーつけた！
Found you!
恋はもう誰にも止められないの
Nobody can stop this love anymore,
好き好き 大好き マリーミー！
I love you, I love you so much, marry me!
二人だけの愛の巣から
From our very own love nest,
逃がさない ずっと
I'll never let you escape, forever.
永遠の愛を誓いましょう
Let's swear eternal love,
神様参拝 飛び跳ねるよう
As if hopping to worship God,
がまんでいない早行っちゃおー！
I can't wait, let's go quickly!
ゴートゥーヘブン！
Go to heaven!
檻の中に
Inside a cage,
囚われて
captured,
凍り付いたマイラブ
my frozen love.
健やかなるときも 病めるときも
In sickness and in health,
命ある限り
as long as I live,
ラブラブチュチュすることを誓います！
I swear to be 'love-love-chu-chu' with you!
世界で一番愛してるよ
I love you more than anyone in the world!
ベイビーもう私を一人にしないで
Baby, don't leave me alone anymore,
あなたがいないとダメなの
I can't go on without you.
寂しがり屋な私の
For someone as lonely as me,
そばにいてずっと
stay by my side forever.
皆様！ 愛してるよー！
Everyone! I love you!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの
My heart is pounding, my love won't stop.
好き好き 大好き マリーミー！
I love you, I love you so much, marry me!
私だけのお姫様も
Even my very own princess,
離さない ずっと
I'll never let go, forever.
境界で四季をあげましょう
Let's offer up the seasons at the boundary,
神様だって怖くない
even God is not scary.
思い立ったので行っちゃおー！
I've made up my mind, so let's go!
ハネムーン！
Honeymoon!
チュッ！ お嫁 ハネムーン！
Chu! Bride honeymoon!
ありがとう！ダーリン！
Thank you, Darling!
チュッ！
Chu!
マリンちゃんめっちゃ中〜〜〜〜きぃ〜〜〜〜！
Marine-chan, we love you so much!
ないない 足りない ないない
Not enough, not enough
ないない 船から ないない
Not here, from the ship, not here
背に腹代えられない
Can't be helped
MONEY OVER BOARD!
Yen Dollar Pound Euro Money Shuki Shuki
Yen Dollar Pound Euro Money, love love
Rupee Rial Won Dong Money Money Money Money
ハイ！
Hai!
寄ってらっしゃいなったら おいでなさい社長様
Step right up, come on over, Mr. CEO
お宝売りますれら Let's Go Auction!
I'll sell you some treasures, let's go auction!
どこぞの旗 No.2
Some random flag, No. 2
オンボロパーカー No.3
A tattered hoodie, No. 3
リップに眼帯は使用済み
Used lipstick and eye patch
How Much? (100万!) (1000万!)
How much? (1 million!) (10 million!)
からの? (1億!) (10億!)
And then? (100 million!) (1 billion!)
からの? (1兆!) (10兆!)
And then? (1 trillion!) (10 trillion!)
もうひとこえ
One more bid!
How Much? (2000!)
からの? (2兆!) (20兆!)
And then? (2 trillion!) (20 trillion!)
からの? (3兆!) (30兆!)
And then? (3 trillion!) (30 trillion!)
ぶっとび! (5000兆!)
Crazy! (5 quadrillion!)
欲しい欲しいマニマニ
Want it, want it, money money
助けて欲しいシャイシャイ
Want help, shy shy
絶頂 Honey Money Bar
Peak Honey Money Bar
バレバレバレバレバレパイレ
Caught, caught, caught, caught, caught pirate
売り出せやお宝ドパドパパパ
Sell those treasures, flow flow flow
サインでもチュキ来い 承認降臨
Even with a signature, come love, approval descent
なんてね!
Just kidding!
だらだら欲望掻き出され
Dripping desire is scraped out
べらべら煩悩満たされ
Chattering worldly desires are filled
ドキドキハラハラこいこいくるくる
Pounding heart, suspense, come come, spin spin
世界が回されて
The world is being spun around
超絶チャーミングな You Have Money
Super charming, you have money
いざハマー!
Now, hammer!
Congratulations!
Yen Dollar Pound Euro Money Shuki Shuki
Yen Dollar Pound Euro Money, love love
Rupee Rial Won Dong Money Money Money Money
ハイ！
Hai!
どこから出たの これアルマルフッチ
Where'd this come from? It's Armani or Gucci?
貝殻トメキンギンド
Shells, stop-gold-silver-copper
お宝売って入金やって
Sell the treasure, get the payment
オフ会誘ってハピピ
Invite to an off-line meetup, happy-pi
出航して嵐に遭って
Set sail and meet a storm
バッタンキュー!
Down for the count!
難破して孤島で見っけ
Shipwrecked and found on a deserted island
あらま幸運 これぞお宝
Oh my, such luck, this is the treasure!
大発見!
A great discovery!
これはマリンが命名する ズンバ
This, Marine will name: Zumba
愛よ地球 No.4
Love for the Earth, No. 4
パンチの報告 No.5
Punch report, No. 5
喉枯れスカーフ No.6
A dry-throat scarf, No. 6
まだ足りない
Still not enough
脱ぎ捨てブーツ No.7
Cast-off boots, No. 7
サービスサービス No.8
Service, service, No. 8
生ママポッキーの魚拓
A gyotaku of fresh mama Pocky
How Much? (100万!) (1000万!)
How much? (1 million!) (10 million!)
からの? (1億!) (10億!)
And then? (100 million!) (1 billion!)
からの? (1兆!) (10兆!)
And then? (1 trillion!) (10 trillion!)
もうひとこえ
One more bid!
How Much? (2000!)
からの? (2兆!) (20兆!)
And then? (2 trillion!) (20 trillion!)
からの? (3兆!) (30兆!)
And then? (3 trillion!) (30 trillion!)
ぶっとび! (5000兆!)
Crazy! (5 quadrillion!)
ド・キ・ド・キ・してRouge？
My heart's pounding, rouge?
いきますよ〜！
Here we go!
(無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！)
(Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!)
(マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！)
(Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!)
(やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ)
(After all, sparkling, more dizzy)
【ねえ、言ったよね？年齢なんて関係ないってさ】
Hey, you said it, right? That age doesn't matter.
【そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって】
That you'd love me including those troublesome parts.
【ねえねえ、言ったよね？ 言ってない？】
Hey, hey, you said it, right? You didn't?
【ふーん、そういうこというんだ。ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？】
Hmm, so that's what you say. By the way, on this ship, beautiful girl innocence is applied, you know?
まかせて！ 魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenation with magic
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ【トクベツですよ〜？】
My secret true face is only for you... it's special, okay?
Ah... アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm troublesome
Ah... 港なんかじゃはしゃげないわ 近頃はね
Ah... I can't frolic at the harbor or anywhere lately
宝の島にしてほしい気分
I feel like I want to make it a treasure island
(出航ー！！)
(Setting sail!!)
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocent
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming for your number one, steady as she goes!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
Actually I'm not confident, but I'll do my best
(Ahoy！！)
(Ahoy!!)
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyurun
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurunrun
恋する気持ち17歳
Loving feelings, 17 years old
0時(テッペン)になっちゃうワ オトナの時間
It's becoming midnight, adult time
(やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ)
(Still sparkling, even more dizzy)
ド・キ・ド・キ・してRouge？
My heart's pounding, rouge?
【あぁ、お許しくだた〜い！このマリンの……】
Ah, please forgive me! This Marine's...
(魅力！ 魔力！ 不可抗力！)
(Charm! Magic! Force majeure!)
──“罪な女”ね？
...is a "sinful woman", isn't she?
離さないで つかまっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight
世界の広さ 見せたげるから！
Because I'll show you how wide the world is!
(出航ー！！)
(Setting sail!!)
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocent
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming for your number one, steady as she goes!
冗談も大好きだけど 真剣よ
I love jokes too, but I'm serious
(Ahoy！！)
(Ahoy!!)
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyurun
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurunrun
恋する気持ち17歳
Loving feelings, 17 years old
0時(テッペン)になっちゃうワ オトナの時間
It's becoming midnight, adult time
(やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ)
(Still sparkling, even more dizzy)
ド・キ・ド・キ・してRouge？
My heart's pounding, rouge?
まだ早い
Still early
(無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！)
(Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!)
(マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！)
(Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!)
(やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ)
(Still sparkling, even more dizzy)
【“マリン”じゃなくて“マリン船長”だろぉん！？】
It's not "Marine", it's "Captain Marine", right!?
音乃瀬 奏
[Otonose Kanade]
一条 莉々華
[Ichijou Ririka]
儒烏風亭 らでん
[Juufuutei Raden]
轟 はじめ
[Todoroki Hajime]
神彩の花びらを
The divinely colored petals...
ある人は美しいと呟いた
...someone once muttered, "They are beautiful."
この地球の横顔は
The profile of this Earth,
どう見えてる？ 君の世界では
how does it look in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなものだけ振り落とした
I shook off only the things I was about to lose.
掌で拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to pick them up in my palm,
指の隙間 すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and vanished.
形あるものだけが全てじゃないけど
Things with form aren't everything, but...
形あるものがどうしたって欲しいよ
...I want things with form, no matter what.
この世界を
This world...
変えることは
...to change it...
きっとできないけど
...I probably can't, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
I should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて 咲いてみて 誇れて
Budding, blooming, being proud,
何一つ欠かせないから
because not a single thing is expendable.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
then that's all I need.
言葉を紡ぐ人
People who spin words,
優しさを編む人
people who knit kindness...
それぞれの正義を分かってあげたい
I want to understand each of their justice.
徒な 矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Vain contradictions and rationalizations,
そんな切なを抱え 今日を生きて
clutching such sorrow, living through today.
分け合った明かり
The light we shared,
隣から隣へ
from neighbor to neighbor,
やがて一つに
eventually becoming one...
夜の帳へ
Into the veil of night,
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life.
君とじゃなきゃダメなんだ
It has to be with you.
このまま寝てしまうには
To just fall asleep like this,
勿体ないほど
it's almost a waste...
優しさにくるまった
Wrapped in kindness,
夜だった
it was such a night.
ハッキリ浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The clearly emerging silhouette of a dream,
それは確かに愛だった
that was certainly love.
月が見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon,
一生のアタッチメント
a lifelong attachment.
煌めく星
The twinkling stars...
鮮やかで 温度や響き
Vividly, the temperature and resonance...
何もかもが僕らだけ
Everything is just for us.
きっと最後に歌まで繋げて
I'll surely connect it all to a song in the end.
この世界を
This world...
変えることは
...to change it...
きっとできないけど
...I probably can't, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
I should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて 咲いてみて 誇れて
Budding, blooming, being proud,
何一つ欠かせないから
because not a single thing is expendable.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
then that's all I need.
Just be by your side.
みんな聴いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for listening!
楽しんでくれましたかー？
Did you all have fun?
ステージ4、まだまだ続きまーす！
Stage 4 is still going!
盛り上がっていこうぜー！
Let's keep the energy up!
いぇーい！
Yeah!
ただいまー！
I'm back!
7th fes. ステージ4、始まりましたー！
7th fes. Stage 4 has begun!
いぇーい！
Yeah!
エキスポ、フェス最終日だよ！
It's the final day of the Expo and Fes!
まだまだ行けるよねー！
We can still keep going, right?
いぇーい！
Yeah!
ちょっとね、今歌って踊ったばかりで、疲れて、ないです！
You know, I just sang and danced, but I'm NOT tired!
まだまだ元気モリモリー！
I'm still full of energy!
元気モリモリー！
Full of energy!
すごい元気だね。
You're really energetic.
でもこんなにさ、たくさんの声援を浴びたらさ、もうパワーもらえちゃうよね。
But when we get this much cheering, we just get so much power.
本当にさ。でもまだまだステージは続いていきますので、
Truly. But the stage will continue on, so...
皆さん右肩上がりで、もっとでかい声！
everyone, let's ramp it up with even louder voices!
楽しんでるー！？
Are you guys having fun!?
ありがとー！
Thank you!
じゃあ、ちょっと自己紹介からさせていただきます！
Well then, let's start with some self-introductions!
可愛いポジティブ、ジニアス！
Cute, positive, genius!
ジニアス！
Genius!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ホロライブデバイス、
リグロスの 一条リリカだよ！
So happy! I'm Ichijou Ririka
from hololive DEV_IS, ReGLOSS!
こんりりー！
Konriri!
わー、めっちゃ嬉しい！
Wow, I'm so happy!
そして！
And!
ホロライブデバイス所属、リグロスの、
奏でる音は奏でる音！音乃瀬奏です！
From hololive DEV_IS, ReGLOSS, the sound played
is the sound played! I'm Otonose Kanade!
なに？なに？なに？えー！
What? What? What? Ehh!
さっきまでさ、あんだけ一緒に
Until just now, you were saying...
「ちょっとドキドキするね」とか言ってたのに！
本番強っ！
...how nervous you were! You're good under pressure!
皆さん、楽しんでますかー！？
Everyone, are you having fun!?
わー！ペンライトも、リリかなの色にしてくれてる！
Wow! You've even turned your penlights
to Riri-Kana's colors!
ねー、すごい！ありがとー！
Right? It's amazing! Thank you!
はい、ということで。
Alright, then.
もう既に、何曲かみんなに、
お披露目できたと思うんですけど。
I think we've already been able to
show you a few songs.
今回、ちょっとSEVEN'S FESのテーマとして、
Ridin' on Dreamsということで。
Since the theme for SEVEN'S FES
is "Ridin' on Dreams"...
ステージと皆さんの客席の、架け橋の形が
トロッコとして、出てきました！
...the "bridge" between the stage and your seats
appeared in the form of a trolley!
すごかったよー！
It was amazing!
実際に私たちも乗らせてもらったんですけど、本当に
みんなの笑顔が、嬉しそうな顔が見えました！
We actually got to ride it too, and we could really
see everyone's smiles and happy faces!
見えてたよー！もうめっちゃ見えてたよ、
顔とか持ってるグッズとか。最高！
I could see you! I could see you so well—
your faces, the goods you're holding. It's the best!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
もうね、せっかくMC務めさせていただいたから、
なんかやりたいことあるんじゃないの？
Well, since we've been given this chance to be MCs,
isn't there something you want to do?
あねー！
A-ne!
社長、何やりたい？
Boss, what do you want to do?
いやもう、一番最初の全体曲の時から、みんなのね、
掛け声とかペンライトとかが、ぶわーって！
Well, ever since the very first group song,
everyone's calls and penlights were just... whoosh!
ぶわーって嬉しいくらい来て、ちょっとそれを、
このMC中にもちょっとやりたいんですけど、いいですかー！？
It was so overwhelming in a good way, and I want to
do a bit of that during this MC too, if that's okay!?
やったー！じゃあリリカは、ペンライトを使って
ちょっとみんなと交流したいです！準備はいいですか？
Yay! Then, I want to use the penlights to interact
with everyone! Are you guys ready?
社長の色、わかるよねー！？
You know my color, right!?
じゃあ、ちょっと全部を、濃いピンク！薄いピンクじゃ
ないですよ、リリカの濃いピンクにしてみていいですか？
Then, could you try turning them all to deep pink!
Not light pink, but Ririka's deep pink, okay!?
もうできてるよー！
They're already doing it!
すごーい！よかったねー！
Amazing! That's great!
お花畑みたい！
It looks like a field of flowers!
じゃあ、次は奏のカラーである、
黄色にしてもらってもいいですかー！？
Then next, could you turn them
to Kanade's color, yellow!?
奏色もしてくれるの？ありがとうー！最高！
You're doing Kanade's color too? Thank you! The best!
じゃあ次は、リリカがピンクって言ったらピンク、
黄色って言ったら黄色にしてね！
Then next, when I say "pink," make it pink,
and when I say "yellow," make it yellow!
できるかなー？できるかなー？うそでしょ？
Can you do it? Can you do it? No way!
いっせーのーで！あ、ピンク変わってるー！
Ready, set... Ah, it changed to pink!
すごい！あ、ちょっとずつ変わってる、どんどん変わってる！
Amazing! Ah, it's changing bit by bit, it's changing more and more!
カチカチカチ、頑張ってる！
Click-click-click, you're doing great!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
じゃあ、好きな色！
Then, your favorite color!
ねー、すごい！お花畑みたい！
ありがとうございます、とっても嬉しいです！
Wow, amazing! It looks like a field of flowers!
Thank you so much, I'm very happy!
じゃあ奏は何やりたい？
Then, what does Kanade want to do?
奏はもう分かってると思うけど、奏がちょっと
このDay 3のMCとして出たということは...
I think you already know, but the fact that I'm here
as an MC for Day 3 means...
今日何曜日だったかなー？奏が『明日は？』って言ったら、
一番のでっかい声で『月曜日！』って叫んでください！
What day is it today? When I say "Tomorrow is...?",
please shout "Monday!" with your loudest voice!
月曜日ですよ、いきますよ！
It's Monday, here we go!
明日はー！？
Tomorrow is...!?
月曜日ーーー！！
MONDAY!!!
最高！ありがとう！
The best! Thank you!
いや、でも明日が月曜日でも、そんな疲れを吹っ飛ぶくらい
今日は最高のパフォーマンスをみんなで届けていきます！
Even if tomorrow is Monday, we're going to deliver the
best performance today to blow away that exhaustion!
盛り上がっていきますよー！
Let's keep the excitement going!
いいねー
Nice!
もっといけるよねー！
You can do more, right?!
まだまだいけるよねー！
You can still do more, right?!
いけるいける！
Yeah, you can!
最高！
Awesome!
はい、ということで、あのね
Alright, so, you know...
今回現地に来てくださってるみんなと 配信で見てくださっているみんなも
Everyone here at the venue today,
and everyone watching the stream too...
そう、コメントも見えてますからね！
Yeah, we can see your comments too!
見えておりますので
We sure can!
配信のみんなは、ハッシュタグ
For everyone on the stream, use the hashtag...
#ホロライブフェスエキスポ26Day3 でたくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいです！
post lots with #hololiveFesExpo26Day3,
we'd be so happy!
嬉しいですー！
We'd be so happy!
いいねー！
Nice!
そしてそして、楽しいお知らせがあるんですけども
And, and, we have a fun announcement...
楽しいお知らせ？！何何ー？！
A fun announcement?! What is it?!
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでー！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok,
this is the end!
えー！どうしよう！
What?! No way!
どうしようー！
Oh no!
はい、でもね、よかったら皆さんまだまだ
Alright, but, if you'd like, everyone...
楽しいライブは続きますので 引き続き見てもらえると嬉しいです！
the fun live performance will continue,
so we'd be happy if you keep watching!
はい、いっぱい声出して応援してね！
Yes, cheer for us with all your might!
応援してください！
Please cheer for us!
それではですね、ちょっと次の曲に入りたいと思いますので
Well then, we're about to move on
to the next song...
せーの、って言ったらみんなで 今回のテーマである
So when I say "Ready, set...",
I'd like everyone to shout...
「Ridin' on Dreams」と叫んでもらえたら嬉しいです。いいですかー？！
the theme for this event, "Ridin' on Dreams".
Are you ready?!
いいですかー？！
オーケー！
Okay!
それじゃあいくよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!!
引き続き楽しんでってねー！
Keep on enjoying the show!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
Supported By LAWSON
[Visual Text: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
Supported By LAWSON]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[Visual Text: The sneak peek part of the show
has ended. Thank you for watching.]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[Text: The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!]
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう!
Come on, let's hop on!
Ridin' on Dreams Yeah!!
Wow oh oh…
Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To something I could never have imagined
想いになったんだ
My feelings have grown so much
わくわく止まらない!
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
We can blow it all away
果てない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There will be difficulties while we're rowing
それも力に変えて
Let's turn those into strength too
一緒に進むんだよ!
And move forward together!